# Diwyanee Awate

#### **MBA** in HR and Marketing

Pune, Maharashtra diwyaneeawate0110@gmail.com +91 95456 24545

Hey! I'm who you're looking for!! I've 3.5 yrs of experience in Teaching and deep love and interest for HR and Marketing field. I've ability to negotiate with excellent communication skills with extensive interest in recruitment. I've enthusiasm to learn new things and always like to try to do my best in it and get appreciated as well performer.

My Career Objective: To work within a well known organisation for self growth and organisational growth. Also to enhance all my skills and knowledge for the betterment of organisation. And to learn new things and explore my knowledge to the extreme!

Willing to relocate to: Pune, Maharashtra - -

#### Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1998-10-01 Eligible to work in: India

**Highest Career Level:** 1-2 years experience

**Industry:** Human Resources

# Work Experience

#### **Talent Scout**

Boyd & Moore Executive Search - Pune, Maharashtra May 2021 to Present

- To attract clients and hire on Executive level position
- Manage hiring process
- Keep track of client's needs and add manage hiring according to same.

#### **Talent Acquisition Representative**

Amdocs - Pune, Maharashtra January 2021 to April 2021

I worked with Amodocs as Talent Acquisition Representative where I learnt about scheduling interviews, Sourcing candidates, Keeping the track of interviewed candidates. Overall to say it was an good experience, learning and understanding the role of recruiter in an organisation.

#### **HR Trainee and Recruiter**

Azieen Consultancy Pvt Ltd - Pune, Maharashtra May 2020 to July 2020

I worked with Azieen Consultancy Pvt Ltd, as an HR Recruiter and Trainee. Where I developed my HR recruiting skills and interview skills. Wherein I learnt a lot about Sourcing candidates and hiring them.

It was an great experience to work with Azieen. Also, in the meantime I made a project and data analysis on "Impact of Covid-19 on Talent Acquisition and Development"

#### **English Lecturer**

Awale Bhaisare Coaching Classes - Pune, Maharashtra September 2016 to December 2019

I was associated with Awale Bhaisare coaching classes as English teacher faculty for 3.5 years. I had a great experience to handle students as well as understand parents and their psychology. I was associated with 9th, 10th (SSC,CBSE) and 11th, 12th students along with Graduation students for English teaching and spoken English faculty. Overall it was a great and amazing experience!

#### Education

#### MBA in HR and Marketing (Management)

SAVITRIBAI PHULE PUNE UNIVERSITY - Pune, Maharashtra August 2019 to May 2021

# Bachelor's in Business Adminstration and Computer Application in Commerce ( Coding )

Savitribai Phule Pune University - College - Pune, Maharashtra July 2016 to June 2019

#### **Higher Secondary(12th Pass) in Science**

Vidya Bhavan High School and Jr. College, St. Anthony's Church - Pune, Maharashtra June 2006 to April 2016

#### Skills / IT Skills

- Public Speaking (Communication Skills)
- · Marketing
- Talent Acquisition
- · HR Management
- Teaching
- Counselling
- · MS office
- Recruitment and Interview skills
- English
- Communication skills
- Tutoring

#### Languages

- English Expert
- Hindi Fluent
- Marathi Expert

• Japanese - Intermediate

# Awards / Achievements

#### **Best Anchor**

March 2020

### **Best Manager**

April 2018

#### College Placement Head (MBA)

December 2020

# **College Fest Organizer (MBA)**

February 2020

#### **Most Enthusiastic Student**

September 2021

# Certifications and Licenses

# **Business Etiquette**

Present

#### **Interview Skills**

Present

#### **Communication Skills**

Present

#### **E-mail Etiquettes**

Present

#### Introduction to soft skills

Present

# **Digital Marketing**

Present

# **Performance Management and Competency mapping**

Present

#### **Product and Brand Management**

Present

#### Philosophical approach to ethics

Present

#### **Public Relations**

Present

# **Leadership and Management**

Present

# Social media marketing

Present

# **Cyber security**

Present

# **Teaching assistant**

Present